Excuse me, sir. Sir, question for you. How
old were you when you made your first million?
My million?
Yes, sir.
That's personal.
If I ever made my million,
you need to talk to him.
Right here, sir. Real quick. Real quick, sir. What
do you do for living out here in Washington, D.C.?
I work in this building.
Capitol?
Yeah, in the Capitol building.
What do you do?
I'm a member of the United States Congress.
I represent the 10th District of Georgia.
Are you a representative?
Yeah.
What's your name?
Mike. I'm Mike Collins.
Mike Collins?
Yeah. The Lake and Riley Act was
my deal. I'm a member of Congress.
You're a member of Congress?
Yes.
Are you serious?
Yes. 100%.
What's your name?
Byron Donalds.
Why did you want to become a
member of Congress? Because you didn't have to.
No.
You had a business, and politics
is a nasty game for people.
Oh, it's hugely nasty.
Well, you say politics is a nasty
game, but politics is how you change things.
I got into politics because people died for
me to have the right to be here.
You've seen some people get real rich off of politics.
Former Speaker Pelosi has done quite well
in the stock market. People don't know why.
What was your first moment in Washington, D.C., when
you were like, oh, this is how this really works?
Oh, man. That was probably our third day here.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What happened?
Well, so actually...
Guys, I'm in Washington, D.C. for
the first time ever to do interviews.
And today, I'm going to be going around
Capitol Hill in D.C. to find and interview politicians
to figure out how they became
wealthy before and maybe even after politics
and what the government knows that we don't.
So stay tuned from start to finish
because this video is about to be insane.
But let's get this thing on the way. Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
How old were you when you made your first million?
I don't know.
Sorry. We don't have time for this.
Real quick. So I have the biggest business
media channel in the world with 14 million followers.
I've interviewed Shaquille O'Neal, Mark
Cuban, the CEO of Nike.
Could we get 30 seconds with you for the channel?
It's to help inspire the
younger generation. Just career advice.
All right. Thank you. Who are you guys with?
The School of Hard Knocks. I started the
biggest business media channel in the entire world.
Congrats. We got to run to a meeting.
All right. Real quick. Are you an entrepreneur?
We got to run to a meeting.
All right, brother. Have a good one.
All right. Thank you.
Excuse me, guys.
Hi there.
Question for you. Who is the richest person here?
Oh, man. Good question.
So you're talking financially?
Financially.
Or are you talking just in life?
Any business owners here?
No.
No? What did you guys do?
I'm not up for this right now.
Excuse me, sir. How old were
you when you made your first million?
I'm good.
What line of business were you in?
What was I in? Am I in?
What do you do for a living?
What is that?
It's a mic.
So I started the biggest business
media channel in the entire world.
I go all over the world
to get advice for the younger generation.
Career mentorship advice from people
that have been there before.
What do you do for a living?
Have a good one, guys. Have a good one.
So as you guys can see, since
we're in Washington, D.C., outside of the Capitol,
it is very hard to get
these people to stop and do interviews.
They're coming and going from meeting to meeting.
And these people do not want to give it away.
But as you know, I'm not going to stop
until I get a million dollars worth of gain
from these politicians to figure out
what they did to build their wealth
before and even after politics just for you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, question for you.
How old were you when you made your first million?
My million?
Yes, sir.
So I started the big...
You're the biggest business media channel
in the world out of Austin, Texas
to help inspire the younger generation.
Could I get one minute with you
on some advice for the younger generation?
I haven't made my million.
You need to talk to him.
Right here, sir.
Real quick.
Real quick, sir.
Thank you.
So, sir, I go all
over the world interviewing successful entrepreneurs,
people that made it for the younger generation.
What did you do to become wealthy?
Well, I started my first business
when I was 23 years old.
Can we pause for a quick second?
No, I've got to catch a plane.
We'll walk with you.
You don't have to walk.
I got you.
So what was that business that you started?
I was in the trucking business.
Still am.
The trucking business.
I own one truck.
We run over 100 a day.
I also have a brokerage company.
How did you buy your first truck?
How did you get the
money to buy your first truck?
You know what?
I went to my community bank.
Yeah?
Small community bank.
What was that conversation like with the bank?
How did you get the money to buy that truck?
Well, it's because the people...
Back then, community banks knew their customer.
They knew the people because
they were part of the community.
Yeah.
I mean, that's the people you saw
on the signs at the baseball fields
or grilling the hamburgers.
And that's been a huge problem
because community banks have been decimated.
And the federal government has been on a
tear to get rid of all the community banks
and the community banks.
And just consolidate down to the point where one day,
you're just going to be dealing with a government bank.
Yeah.
And when we get to that
point, you're going to be in trouble.
But I tell all young people, man,
you know, if you have an idea
or you want to do something, the
best thing you can do is work hard.
Yeah.
Work every day.
Work your ass off.
Yeah.
So what are you doing in D.C.?
I represent the 10th District of Georgia.
Are you a representative?
Yeah.
In the U.S. level?
What's your name?
Mike.
I'm Mike Collins.
Mike Collins?
Yeah.
The Lake and Riley Act was my bill.
Actually.
Yeah.
So what's an economic truth that most...
Most politicians are afraid to admit?
The fact that free market works.
The free marketplace is beyond unbelievable.
Capitalism?
Yes.
And President Trump knows that.
And the other fact that President Trump
knows is that we need small businesses.
A small business needs big business.
Yeah.
But without a small business and
the ability to be an entrepreneur,
to start from the ground
up and work your way up,
work your ass off to get there,
you know, people really don't have an incentive.
You think about what the Obama administration,
what the Biden administration, both
of them tried to accomplish.
I mean, inflation went through the roof.
They didn't want you owning a house.
They don't want young people owning homes.
They want you renting apartments.
Hell, they don't even really want you owning an EV.
They want you to ride on mass transit.
They don't want you to have your own health care.
They want you to have government health care.
They want everything you do for you
to look for the government for the answer.
And that's not America.
It's not in God we trust.
We look to God for those answers.
But if they feel like that
they can get you into that position,
all you'll work for is enough money to get by.
Pay to rent.
Pay to bus fare.
That's not the American dream, though.
No.
No, it's not.
It's not.
So you've got to stand up.
You've got to stand up for small business.
You've got to stand up for the free market.
At your business, in terms of revenue,
what's the most amount of money
you made in a single year?
Well, somewhere between the $20 million and $50 million.
I'll put it that way.
So you're big millions.
We've been very fortunate.
How did you scale?
I was willing to take the chance.
You took some risks.
Yeah.
99% of people won't take the risk.
They just won't do it.
Why did you want to become a member of Congress?
Because you didn't have to.
No.
You had a business.
And politics is a nasty game for people.
It's hugely nasty.
Is there a lot of corruption?
I don't know about the corruption side.
I really don't know.
People ask me that all the time.
I don't go for that, so I don't know.
But I knew I could take my experience up here.
I could serve the people, not just the 10th District,
not just in Georgia, but the whole country,
and try to get us back to where we were.
Plus, I was in business during the Trump administration,
the first one.
We still are.
I mean, I know what
it felt like under Biden, too.
But I also know what it
felt like to win during Trump.
I've been in business since George H.W. Bush.
So I've been through them all.
Do you believe in God?
Oh, yeah.
Has faith been important for you?
Yeah, huge.
How so?
Well, I mean,
think about it, man.
You're going to have things happen in your life,
good or bad.
And if you don't have that rock to lean on,
I don't know what you're going to lean on.
There's things that's happened to me up here.
I can't explain it.
But hey, I know where it came from.
So you see miracles happen.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I see things happen in my life that I'm like,
dude, I don't know how that happened to me.
But I was here, and
I was in the right place.
And the good Lord opened the door.
He opened the door, you walked through it.
The trucking business is competitive.
What did you do to stand out?
The number one thing you do?
Service.
Work your tail off.
Beyond that, though, because you can work hard
and beyond the hard work.
People notice that, though.
They notice that.
I had people calling me asking me because
maybe we weren't the biggest.
We weren't.
But when you deliver and you do what you say
you're going to do, even if things happen
and you compensate and you push things around,
you do what you say and you do that continuously.
People reward you for that.
They do that up here, too.
If we would just do our job.
I mean, I'm the first freshman to get a bill
signed into law.
I've had two bills signed into law in two years
by two different presidents for two different parties.
I got a role, man.
I got a plan.
Your last message to the younger generation.
Give them one more little nugget.
Keep the faith.
Keep the faith, man.
It's available.
It's hard.
It's probably harder than what
it was when I was there.
We're going to do what
we can to get this government
off your back and out of your back pocket.
But go for it, man.
The number one lesson I learned, it's at the base
of my flagpole in my office.
It says, can't, never could.
You believe you can't, you'll never do anything.
Believing that you can is way more profitable
than believing that you can't.
Dang, she's getting me, man.
I love it, man.
Just believe it.
Remind me your name one more time.
Collins.
Thank you for stopping, sir.
Guys, we're right outside of the Capitol building
and we just come up on an absolute business mogul
in the trucking industry.
And he's now a congressman.
He's in the House of Representatives
for the state of Georgia.
And he passed one of the biggest and most known
pieces of legislation that's gone through
in the last couple of years.
Mike Collins, I believe his name was,
just gave an awesome interview for us here
at the School of Hard Knocks.
We got to keep this one rolling, man.
Go get another one, you guys.
Come on, let's go.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Thank you, brother.
Real quick, real quick.
How old were you when you made your first million?
I'm not old enough yet.
Yeah?
What line of business are you in?
What do you do for a living?
I'm a member of the United States Congress.
House or Senate?
House.
Actually.
Let me ask you this.
What were you doing prior to getting into politics?
Trying to help people.
That's what I did.
Started out.
There's only like 500 or so people
in the U.S. House of Representatives.
What was the biggest driving factor of your success?
A lot of people dream to do that one day.
We're trying to inspire the younger generation.
We've got 14 million followers.
I've interviewed Shaquille O'Neal, Mark Cuban,
the biggest business owners to help younger people.
Just one minute of your time, real quick.
Look, I just think to
know that you're in this country,
that you have a responsibility to give back to it,
and that you can make a difference.
I grew up in public housing, poor,
but I saw changes that could be made
by just contributing and working with people.
What was that first actionable step that you took
to start changing your family's trajectory?
You said you didn't come from money,
but you actually made it to
one of the highest levels of offices
that you can hold in the United States.
Well, for me, the first thing was education,
and my family was important,
and then reading was important,
and learning what was going on around my own environment,
and then saying, how can I make a difference?
And talking to some of my friends,
and then seeing some of my friends
who actually are not here anymore,
who were killed, who started using drugs
or something of that nature.
You believe in God?
I'm here only because of God.
How important has faith been for you?
Faith is real.
Very important.
For all of my life, faith has been important.
Is it part of your decision-making process?
It is.
Absolutely.
How have you leaned on his understanding
as opposed to your own,
and how do you incorporate that into your daily life?
Because some people say that they believe in God,
but really, how do you leverage
and use that in your daily life?
I think about what I'm doing,
and I think about the Bible,
and look at, for example, the works of Dr. King,
who I believe was an angel from God,
and how he lived his life in that regard.
And I challenge myself to try to accomplish
and to live up to those things,
to do what I think,
and to do what I believe
is the right thing to do,
the godly thing to do,
the humanitarian thing to do.
Politics is a nasty game.
You know, like, why did
you want to get into politics?
Well, you say politics is a nasty game,
but politics is how you change things.
I got into politics because people died
for me to have the right to be here.
Ministers, rabbis, imams,
arm and arm in the civil rights movement,
and that whole movement was about getting more people here.
So if folks would put their lives on the line
and saying that that's how we
make this place that we live in
and this planet a better place,
then that's for me to do.
I'm 70.
You look like 45.
I wish I was.
How do you look so good for 70 years old?
You seem very young and fit.
Number one, faith does happen,
and two, you have to exercise,
and you have to do
those things that make the sacrifices
that's good for your body.
Take care of your body.
Watch what you eat.
You know, all of that's important.
I'm in my early 20s,
so you got 40 plus years on me.
Let's break that learning curve right here.
We can collapse time.
Give me one piece of advice
that you would pass on to me
so that way when I'm 70 years old,
I look forward and I'm proud
of the life that I live.
Give me a nugget, something that really helped you out,
maybe some of the best advice that you got
that you could pass on to somebody else as well
to help them in whatever
career or industry that they're in.
I give you what I tell my daughters.
The first thing is you gotta believe in yourself.
How did you find that initial self-belief?
What happened is when you start thinking,
can I, can I accomplish, can I do this?
Is this important?
And believe that you can.
Can I make a change?
Can I make a difference?
And believe that you can.
If you think that it doesn't make a difference,
that you're not there,
and I think that one of
the things that has impacted me,
and I say to my daughter,
I believe everybody has a purpose.
And so one of the keys
to life is finding your purpose.
God's put you here for a reason.
It's no accident that you're here.
And the important part is finding what your purpose is.
And when you find out what your purpose is,
when you can feel it,
because you can feel it,
because you're destined to do it,
some people know what their purpose is
and run away from it.
They get afraid of what their purpose is.
They think it's too hard for them to accomplish
what their purpose is.
But once you find it,
let nothing take you off track.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you so much for your time.
Thank you for what you do.
Gregory Meeks.
Gregory Meeks, I appreciate you.
All right, man.
Seriously, that was a strong interview.
I love that, man.
Thank you. Thank you, my friend.
Have a great day.
Thank you.
My man just...
Sup, brother?
I love, love, love, love, love, love your Instagram.
Gregory Meeks is actually a neighbor of mine.
Man, he just gave an incredible interview.
Oh, dude, he's been doing this for years.
Guys, DC has been crazy so far.
And I'm headed to go get my next congressman
outside of the capital here in DC.
But if you guys want direct access
to the millionaires and the billionaires
that I interview on this channel every single week,
I've built and created the number one community
for business owners in the entire world,
where I give you the ability
to hop on live Zoom calls
every single week and get access to the minds
and the skills of the millionaires and billionaires
that I interview.
And for a limited time,
you can join this community right now for free
to come see what it's like
and how much your life would change
if you had the ability to get mentored
from a multimillionaire or billionaire.
So whether you're in a nine to five right now
and you wanna figure out the exact steps it takes
to leave that job and start building
and creating the business of your dreams,
or maybe you've already taken that leap,
you started that business,
you started your entrepreneurial journey,
and you wanna learn directly from somebody
who's actually built and created an eight figure,
nine figure, or billion dollar company,
well, every week,
I have the opportunity inside of my private community
to hop on live calls and speak directly
to the millionaires and billionaires that I interview.
All you have to do to join for free today
is go down to the link
in the description of this video
to become a member of the School of Mentors.
I can't wait to see you on the inside.
With that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
How old were you when you made your first million?
That's personal.
Well, what line of business are you in?
Right now, I'm a representative
for the great state of Montana.
Actually, what were you doing prior
to getting into politics?
And just for context,
I started one of the biggest business media channels
in the world to get advice
for the younger generation.
I'm not here to ask about politics,
just for advice for younger people.
Well, I'll tell you what,
I grew up without anything.
I managed to get to college,
was successful there,
got a job at New York University
as a research scientist.
NYU?
Yeah, NYU.
I taught there for a couple of years,
left there,
did a startup company that I merged with Yahoo
when they first started out.
So Yahoo bought your company?
God bless America.
You said Yahoo bought your company?
We did a pooling of interest merger in the 90s.
My company became Yahoo.
We pooled our shares.
Oh, my goodness.
After that, I tried to help other people
do the same thing,
did a lot of angel financing,
early stage tech venture.
September 11th happened,
I got upset, joined the Air Force,
so I was doing combat search and rescue in Afghanistan,
but I'll say this country's been good to me.
Yeah, I was the unplanned pregnancy
of an unwed teenage mom.
Look what I was able to do.
I think about that girl trying to figure out
what was in store for her.
Raising me obviously gave me life,
gave me faith,
this country gave me opportunity,
God gave me a plan,
and look what I was able to do.
That girl, three months ago,
flew to Washington, D.C.,
and saw her son get sworn into Congress.
God bless America.
Congratulations, sir.
Wait, real quick,
let me ask you this then.
What common mistake do you see business owners
make in today's world
that prevents them from having success?
Well, here's the thing,
the secret to overnight success
is to keep turning the crank.
People take their eye off the ball.
You gotta just keep turning that crank,
keep trying to get the ball down the field.
What happens is people get distracted
and they stop that,
put in the time to do it.
Every overnight success that I know
took years to do it of turning that crank.
So you thought in decades,
not short term,
you thought very long term.
Well, I think you need to think in decades.
You need to just keep working,
pushing that ball forward,
and eventually,
if you have the discipline to do that,
you're gonna look behind you and go,
oh my gosh, look what I built.
I think that's the biggest thing
is they're not focused on that.
You just gotta keep doing,
keep building,
keep showing up.
Back in my tech days,
it was not uncommon for us
to work 20 hours a day.
And I'm not exaggerating.
I mean, you'd sleep here and there
when you couldn't focus anymore.
You'd get your four hours of sleep at night
and you'd just be back working again.
That's what we did.
That's what we all did.
Here's the thing,
people say, oh, you got lucky.
I'm gonna tell you,
the harder you work,
the luckier you get.
But let me ask you this though.
Oh my gosh.
So what are you trying to accomplish in Capitol Hill?
I wanna make sure that the America
that was so good to me,
that made it so that a
kid born to a single mom,
somebody that has no family connections,
no family money,
can do what I was able to do.
And I think that's being squandered.
I think that brass ring
is farther and farther and farther away.
I mean, lack of fiscal constraint.
There's so many things
that have made that harder and harder to do.
We need to claw that back.
I worry how a family starting out now,
somebody starting a small business,
doesn't have to be technology,
any kind of business.
I worry about how that family
ever has a path to buy their first home,
which is the bedrock,
the cornerstone of the American dream.
And we need to fight back.
And I think a big part of it
is just fiscal constraints,
starting to reign things back
so that the United States of America
is the promise that it always has been.
That shining beacon,
that American dream is still possible.
Thank you, sir.
I appreciate you.
Have a great day.
We just got another congressman
out here in the US House of Representatives.
Went from being a professor
to building a startup that was merged with Yahoo,
a multi-billion dollar company.
And again, just gave you guys some incredible advice
for all the entrepreneurs
and the younger generation out there, man.
Washington DC has been crazy, man.
These congressmen are dropping
some straight game for you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yes.
Yeah?
And what do you do for
living out here in Washington DC?
I work in this building.
Capitol?
Yeah, in the Capitol building.
What do you do?
I'm a member of Congress.
You're a member of Congress?
Yes.
Like in the Senate or House of Representatives?
Oh, House, House of Representatives.
You're a representative?
Yep.
In the US level?
Yes.
Are you serious?
What's your name?
Byron Donalds.
Byron Donalds?
Could I interview you for a minute real quick?
I go all over the world interviewing the most successful
people to help the younger generation.
You think I could get a minute
of your time real quick?
Yeah, sure, of course.
Is that okay?
What's the turning point like getting into politics?
Did you always know that
you were gonna become a member
of Congress and work in one of the highest levels
of office that you could possibly hold?
No, my business was in finance.
I was in life settlements,
viaduct settlements at the time.
And when the economy was
kind of blowing up in 2008,
I had to do research for my firm.
And that's when I started watching politics
and getting engaged.
And I was about 30 at the time,
but this was not a dream
as a kid or in college
or nothing like that.
So you have a finance background?
Mm-hmm.
17 years, I'm securities licensed.
What's an economic truth that most politicians
are afraid to say?
Or that they're afraid to admit?
Can't borrow money forever.
The more money we borrow, the more it costs us.
And what most people don't understand
is when you increase the nation's debt,
it actually destroys the purchasing power
of every American.
The people who suffer most are poor people,
seniors on fixed incomes.
So at some point we have to pay that back.
Yeah, at some point we gotta stop borrowing as much.
Right now, let's slow down the trajectory of our borrowings.
Let's get there first and then really plan a way
over the next couple of decades
to start paying down the debt.
How have you made your money work for you?
What are you putting your money into right now?
My firm trades on my behalf.
I don't trade securities.
Why not?
Well, one, I think it's unethical for members to trade.
Because I have information that people don't.
Have you seen a lot of
members of Congress do that before?
Oh, yeah.
Former Speaker Pelosi has done
quite well in the stock market.
People don't know why.
You get a $150 billion
net worth off a $100,000 salary.
You've seen some people get real rich off of politics.
Yeah.
And I think that's really what's messed this place up.
Because that's where I say it becomes about you
and not about the people that sent you.
If you do this job right,
you lose money on this deal.
What was your first moment in Washington, DC,
when you were like, oh,
this is how this really works?
Oh, man.
That was probably our third day here.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What happened?
Well, so actually, when I got sworn in,
the third day I was here was January 6.
So we got sworn in.
Three days later, we were doing the certification
of the 20 election.
And that was a day.
But what have you learned from being in Congress?
Like, you've been behind doors
that most Americans will never
see.
What's something that you've seen
that would shock most people?
I think what would shock people here
is that most members are afraid.
They're afraid of criticism.
They're afraid of make the tough
choice and do the right thing.
It's a tough choice to make in the moment,
but it's going to be the best thing
for the future of the country.
It's one of the things
that makes me kind of sad
about this place.
Because if we just didn't worry about the fear quotient
and actually just were bold and did the right things,
the country would be significantly better off.
Have you seen power corrupt people?
Oh, yeah.
That's why I believe in term limits.
You should not stay here forever.
You got to go home.
Who holds the power in DC?
The president, obviously.
The president, speaker of the House, Senate majority leader.
But I would argue that the real power in DC
is really if a cluster of members
are willing to stand firm for something.
Because at the end of the day, it's
going to be in Washington, everybody's counting votes.
And if you don't have
enough votes to get a majority
to move something off the floor, nothing happens.
What's the toughest decision you had to make in politics?
Oh, man.
When I got nominated for speaker at the beginning
of my second term.
You were at the House?
Yeah, I got nominated.
We were having a difference of agreement
on how the House should operate.
And there were a group of members
that opposed Speaker McCarthy at the time.
And the group was trying
to figure out who to nominate.
And they were like, we want to nominate you.
And I'm like, what?
And so I remember that day so well.
I had to go into the
side room, pray, call my wife.
I think I could really
sense the gravity at the moment.
Because we're trying to select a speaker at the House.
The whole world is watching this thing.
And my name moves forward.
And it's funny, too.
We're over here by the steps.
And I remember Manu Raju, CNN.
We came out after I got nominated.
And we come out on the steps.
And the whole press corps
is coming out this massive gaggle.
And Manu Raju, CNN goes,
are you concerned about retribution?
And I looked at him.
And I just deadpan.
I go, man, I'm 6'2", 275.
I'm not worried about that.
Not worried about it.
I love it.
That was probably a defining moment for me.
What's your long-term goal in politics?
I'm running for governor now.
So we'll see if the
people of Florida will elect me.
Running for governor of Florida?
I am.
So we'll see how that goes.
We feel good.
We feel confident about the race.
But I think in politics, like
in life, you're either moving up
or you're moving out.
And anything that is stagnant doesn't go well in life.
I want you to think back to your career.
What was that one conversation that really
changed your trajectory in life?
Oh, man.
My boss, when I was 29,
he said to me, he said, Byron,
whatever you do, get to work.
That's where you want to get to by 40.
He goes, because by 40, that's where you're really
going to make your money.
That's really where you're going to make your mark.
And when you're young, coming into your career,
you want every promotion.
You want every title.
You want every raise.
But I think those early years
are really just a grind for you
to really know how to work, learn about you,
learn about how to work with other people.
That advice really did sink in.
It does matter.
You really just want to kind of get
to where you want to get to by 40.
And then that's really when you take off.
And so look at me.
I'm 46.
But you don't care about what anybody thinks about you.
No.
Why not?
Haters going to hate you.
Yeah.
That's right, man.
If I have it in my
office, I subscribe to the mama mentality.
Haters are a good problem to have.
You got to learn to love it.
Can't worry about it.
Hey, I don't care if
they love me or hate me
as long as they call me.
That's right.
Do you believe in God?
Yes.
Has faith been important for you?
It's been huge.
I gave my life to Christ at 21.
And I think that I was lost, man.
Did you have some low points?
Oh, yeah.
18, 19, 20, I had some real low points.
Like what?
Got arrested at 18.
Got arrested at 20.
Was really not where I needed to be.
But you didn't fall into that victim mentality.
Because obviously, you didn't let that stop you
from achieving the kind of success you amounted to.
No.
No, no.
Because I had to look myself in the mirror.
And the first decision was, I'm not
going to be in this position ever again.
And that was a decision I made at 20.
You hear the young people say all the time
that the system is rigged.
Do you think it's rigged?
Or are they just missing the playbook?
No, they're missing the playbook.
They didn't open it up.
Run the play.
You gave your life to Christ at 21 years old.
Yeah.
Why did you make that decision that young?
And why has that been such a consistent factor
from 21 to 46 years old?
When I gave my life to Christ, God really
had been dealing with me and my spirit.
At its core, he was
basically like, stop running from me.
What are you running from me for?
I remember I was working.
I was a waiter at Cracker Barrel in college.
And the table I was waiting on was this revival,
a bunch of ladies from a revival and the pastor.
And I asked them to pray over my life.
And they did.
And I gave my life
to Christ in the parking lot
of Cracker Barrel at 21.
And you see miracles happen after that.
I love that.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Thanks.
Thank you so much for your time.
What's your name?
Byron.
Byron?
Yeah.
It's great to meet you.
Pleasure.
Guys, Washington DC was amazing.
This is my first time filming here,
but it definitely won't be my last.
But I need you guys to
like and subscribe for amazing content
I've got coming every single week.
And if you are not a member yet, you
need to go down to the
link in the description of this video
to join the School of Mentors, the number one community
for business owners in the entire world.
And the reason why I built the number one community
for business owners is because every single week,
I give you guys direct access to the multimillionaires
and the billionaires that I interview, where literally you
can join, come in, hop on
live calls, and ask your questions,
and speak directly to the people that I interview,
the millionaires and billionaires
and as you see me interview every week,
I give you direct access to them every single week.
Imagine connecting with a multimillionaire or a billionaire
or getting mentored by one.
Watch what would happen to your life.
All you have to do is go
down to the link in the description.
I can't wait to see you on
the inside of the School of Mentors.
With that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.